Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Athletics, Communications, Records SC0367
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Department of Athletics, Communications, records
1930-2008
bulk
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Department of Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation. Media Relations
SC0367
140.5 Linear Feet
The collection consists of programs, statistics, press releases, scrapbooks, brochures, photographs, slides, video footage, and pamphlets pertaining to football, basketball, wrestling, golf, and other sports at Stanford University,
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Administrative transfers, 1989-2009.
Information about Access
Collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use.
Scope and Content of Collection
The collection consists of programs, statistics, press releases, scrapbooks, brochures, photographs, slides, and pamphlets pertaining to football, basketball, wrestling, golf, and other sports at Stanford University, including two scrapbooks on women's sports at Stanford, 1964-1975. Also included are video tapes of football games, 1970-92; women's basketball games, 1987-99; men's basketball games, 1984-92; miscellaneous tapes of volleyball, swimming, gymnastics, and baseball; interviews with coaches Jack Elway, Dick Gould, Tara VanDerveer, and Mike Montgomery; and campus promotional spots aired during televised games.
Arrangement note
Records are arranged as received.
Biographical / Historical
On March 12, 1975 all men’s and women’s sports programs were merged into a new Department of Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation (DAPER) to better enable the university to comply with Title IX. Stanford's first scholarships for women athletes are awarded in the fall. At the time, the university has 19 intercollegiate teams: 12 for men and seven for women.
College sports -- California.; Sports for women.; Stanford University. Department of Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation. Media Relations; Montgomery, Mike; Stanford University. Department of Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation. Sports Information Office; Elway, Jack; Gould, Dick; Stanford University. Department of Athletics; VanDerveer, Tara
- Records, 1972-1978; Accession ARCH-1984-132
  - Record book for men's golf contests, 1972-78 (Box 1)
  - Bound volumes of Touchdown Illustrated, 1973-76 (Box 2)
  - Bound volumes of Touchdown Illustrated, 1977-78 (Box 3)
- Additional Records, 1931-1983; Accession ARCH-1984-158
  - Clippings
    - Baseball clippings 1980-1981 (Box 1)
    - Baseball clippings 1981-1982 (Box 1)
    - Basketball clippings October 1979-March 1980 (Box 1)
    - Basketball clippings April 1980-July 1981 (Box 1)
    - Football clippings August 1976-November 1977 (Box 2)
    - Football clippings December 1977-May 1978 (Box 2)
    - Football clippings June 1978-October 1978 (Box 2)
    - Football clippings November 1978-March 1979 (Box 3)
    - Football clippings April 1979-October 1979 (Box 3)
    - Football clippings November 1979-April 1980 (Box 3)
    - Football clippings November 1981- May 1982 (Box 4)
    - Football clippings January 1981-October 1981 (Box 4)
    - Football clippings October 1980-December 1980 (Box 4)
    - Football clippings April 1980-October 1980 (Box 4)
    - General Sports clippings April 1977-November 1977 (Box 5)
    - General Sports clippings November 1977-May 1978 (Box 5)
    - General Sports clippings May 1978-March 1979 (Box 5)
    - General Sports clippings March 1979-February 1980 (Box 6)
    - General Sports clippings Winter 1980 (Feb.-Sept.) (Box 6)
    - General Sports clippings Fall 1980 (March 1980-October 1981) (Box 6)
    - Spring Sports clippings 1980-1981 (Box 7)
    - General Sports clippings Fall 1981 (Box 7)
  - Videos
    - Football 1980 preseason, 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 8)
    - Football 1981 preseason show, 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 8)
    - Football vs. Ohio State, Sept. 26, 1981, 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 8)
    - Football at Arizona, Oct. 3, 1981, 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 8)
    - Football vs. UCLA, Oct. 10, 1981, 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 8)
    - Football at USC, Oct. 17, 1981, 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 8)
    - Football vs. Arizona State, Oct. 24, 1981, 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 8)
    - Football at Washington, Oct. 31, 1981, 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 8)
    - Football at Oregon State, Nov. 11, 1981, 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 8)
    - Football vs. Oregon, Nov. 14, 1981, 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 8)
    - Football vs. Cal, Nov. 21, 1981, 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 8)
    - NCAA Productions College Football 1983 Taking the Offensive, 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 8)
    - PAC-10 Basketball Preview, Nov. 8, 1983, 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 8)
    - NCAA Championship 1980 Soccer, Nov. 6, 1981, 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 8)
    - ESPN tapes (1 of 4, and 2 of 4) of " OU/Stanford," no dates, 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 8)
  - Press releases, football, Aug.-Nov. 1979 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Golf records, 1931-38 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Golf records, 1939-46 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Golf records, 1949-1950 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Golf records, 1951-52 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Golf records, 1953-54 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Women's basketball series records, 1974/1975-1983 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Women's volleyball series records, 1976-1982 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Additional Records, 1976-1982; Accession ARCH-1986-143
  - Men's basketball game files (and tournaments), 1979-1982 (Box 1-3)
  - Press releases and "Highs and Lows" for all sports, 1980-82 (Box 4-6)
  - Clippings on football, 1977 (Box 7)
  - Photographs (contact sheets) on football, 1977 and 1978-79 (Box 7)
  - Photographs (contact sheets) on football, 1978 (Box 8)
  - Football slides, 1977-79, with some as early as 1970 (Box 8)
  - Football slides, 1980 (mug shots and action shots) (Box 8)
  - Clippings on men's basketball, 1978 (Box 8)
  - Slides of men's and women's basketball and minor sports, with some campus scenes, 1971-1981 (Box 8)
  - Contact sheets on men's basketball, 1978-79 (Box 8)
  - Slides of men's and women's basketball and minor sports, 1976-1981 (Box 8)
- Additional Records, 1979-1987; Accession ARCH-1989-119
  - Football vs Purdue 9/11/82 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Football vs San Jose State 9/18/82 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Football vs Ohio State 9/25/82 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Football vs Oregon State 10/2/82 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Football vs Arizona State 10/4/82 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Football vs USC 10/16/82 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Football vs Washington State 10/23/82 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Football vs University of Arizona 11/6/82 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Football vs UCLA 11/13/82 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Football vs Oklahoma 9/10/1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Football vs Univ. of Illinois 9/17/1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Football vs San Jose State 9/24/1983 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Football vs Arizona State 10/1/1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Football vs UCLA 10/8/1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Football vs Univ. of Washington 10/15/1983 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Football vs Univ. of Arizona 10/22/1983 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Football vs Oregon State 10/24/1983 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Football vs USC 11/5/1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Football vs Univ. of Washington 10/30/82 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Football vs Oregon State 11/12/1983 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Football vs California 11/19/1983 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Football vs Univ. of Oklahoma 9/8/1984 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Football vs Univ. of Illinois [1984] (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Football vs San Jose State 9/22/1984 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Football vs Arizona State 9/29/1984 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Football vs UCLA 10/6/1984 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Football vs Univ. of Washington 10/13/1984 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Football vs Washington State 10/20/1984 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Football vs Oregon State 10/27/1984 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Football vs USC 11/3/1984 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Football vs Univ. of Arizona 11/10/1984 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Football vs California 11/17/1984 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Football vs San Jose State 9/14/85 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Football vs Univ. of Oregon 9/21/85 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Football vs Texas 9/28/85 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Football vs San Diego State 10/5/85 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Football vs UCLA 10/12/85 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Football vs USC 10/19/85 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Football vs Univ. of Arizona 10/26/85 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Football vs Univ. of Washington 11/2/85 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Football vs Oregon State 11/9/85 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Football vs Arizona State 11/16/85 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Football vs California 11/23/85 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Football vs Texas 9/13/1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Men's basketball Non-conference games, 1982-82 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Men's basketball Non-conference games, 1982-82 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Men's basketball Stanford Invitational 12/3/82 - 12/4/82 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Men's basketball vs Oregon State 1/6/1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Oregon 1/8/1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Men's basketball vs California 1/17/1983 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Men's basketball vs USC 1/20/1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Men's basketball vs UCLA 1/22/1983 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Washington 1/27/1983 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Men's basketball vs Washington State 1/29/1983 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Men's basketball vs Arizona State 2/5/1983 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Arizona 2/7/1983 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Men's basketball vs California 2/12/1983 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Men's basketball vs UCLA 2/17/1983 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Men's basketball vs USC 2/19/1983 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Men's basketball vs Washington State 2/24/1983 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Washington 2/26/1983 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Arizona 3/3/1983 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Men's basketball vs Arizona State 3/5/1983 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Oregon 3/10/1983 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Men's basketball vs Oregon State 3/12/1983 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Men's basketball Hewlett-Packard/Stanford Invitational 12/2/1983 - 12/3/1983 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Men's basketball Non-conference games, 1983-84 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Men's basketball Non-conference games, 1983-84 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Men's basketball vs Oregon State 1/5/1984 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Oregon 1/7/1984 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Men's basketball vs UCLA 1/10/1984 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Men's basketball vs California 1/13/1984 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Men's basketball vs USC 1/19/1984 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Men's basketball vs Oregon State 1/23/1984 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Washington 1/26/1984 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Men's basketball vs Washington (State?) 1/28/1984 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Men's basketball vs Arizona State 2/2/1984 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Men's basketball vs California 2/10/1984 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Men's basketball vs USC 2/17/1984 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Men's basketball vs UCLA 2/18/1984 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Men's basketball vs Washington State 2/23/1984 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Washington 2/25/1984 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Arizona 3/1/1984 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Men's basketball vs Arizona State 3/3/1984 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Oregon 3/8/1984 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Men's basketball vs San Diego State 11/24/1984 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Men's basketball Apple Invitational Tournament 11/30/1984 - 12/1/1984 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Men's basketball vs Missouri-St. Louis 12/4/1984 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Men's basketball vs Seattle University 12/19/1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Men's basketball vs Loyola-Marymount 12/21/1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Men's basketball vs UC-Riverside 12/24/1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Men's basketball vs St. Mary's-Moraga 12/18/1984 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Men's basketball Texas Longhorn Tournament: Mercer, Army 12/28/1984 - 12/29/1984 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Washington 1/3/85 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Men's basketball vs Washington State 1/5/85 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Men's basketball vs Arizona State 1/10/85 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Arizona 1/12/85 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Men's basketball vs California 1/19/85 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Men's basketball vs UCLA 1/26/85 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Men's basketball vs USC 1/28/85 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Oregon 1/31/85 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Men's basketball vs Oregon State 2/2/85 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Arizona 2/7/85 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Men's basketball vs Arizona State 2/9/85 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Men's basketball vs California 2/16/85 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Men's basketball vs UCLA 2/18/85 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Men's basketball vs USC 2/21/85 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Men's basketball vs Oregon State 2/28/85 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Oregon 3/2/85 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Men's basketball vs Washington State 3/7/85 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Washington 3/9/85 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Men's basketball vs Australian Nat'l Team 11/8/85 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Men's basketball vs George Washington University 11/26/85 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Men's basketball CAN/AM challenge 11/27/85 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Men's basketball vs San Diego State 12/2/85 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Men's basketball Apple Invitational (Stanford, Richmond, Yale, St. Mary's) 12/6/85 - 12/7/85 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Men's basketball vs Seattle 12/13/85 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Men's basketball vs Harvard 12/14/85 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Men's basketball vs North Carolina 12/20/85 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Men's basketball vs Seton Hall 12/22/85 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Men's basketball vs UNLV (Chaminade Classic) 12/24/85 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Men's basketball vs Chaminade (Chaminade Classic) 12/25/85 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Men's basketball Hawaii-Pacific Tournament 12/28/85 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Men's basketball vs Washington State 1/2/1986 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Washington 1/4/1986 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Arizona 1/9/1986 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Men's basketball vs Arizona State 1/1//1986 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Oregon 1/13/1986 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Men's basketball vs California 1/18/1986 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Men's basketball vs UCLA 1/23/1986 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Oregon 1/31/1986 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Men's basketball vs Oregon State 2/2/1986 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Men's basketball vs Arizona State 2/6/1986 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Arizona 2/8/1986 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Men's basketball vs California 2/15/1986 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Men's basketball vs USC 2/20/1986 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Men's basketball vs UCLA 2/24/1986 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Men's basketball vs Oregon State 2/27/1986 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Men's basketball vs USC 3/1/1986 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Men's basketball vs Univ. of Washington 3/6/1986 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Men's basketball vs Washington State 3/8/1986 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Tennis - Wrestling Clippings (Box 4)
  - Football Clippings 1982 (Box 4)
  - Football Clippings1983-1984 (Box 4)
  - Football Clippings 1985 (Box 5)
  - Football Clippings 1986 (Box 5)
  - Basketball Clippings 1981-1982 (Box 5)
  - Basketball Clippings 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - Basketball Clippings 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Basketball Clippings 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Spring Sports [clippings] 1982-1983 (Box 7)
  - Baseball [clippings] 1983 (Box 7)
  - Press releases Aug. 13, 1979 - Nov. 10, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 1-17)
  - Press releases Nov. 14, 1981 - Dec. 19, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 1-14)
  - Press releases Jan. 30, 1984 - June 29, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 1-4)
- Additional Records, 1974-1978; Accession ARCH-1989-161
  - Football vsOklahoma 9/9/78 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Football vs San Jose State 9/16/78 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Football vs Illinois 9/23/78 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Football vs Tulane 9/30/78 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Football vs UCLA 10/7/78 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Football vs Washington 10/14/78 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Football vs Washington 10/21/78 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Football vs Oregon State 10/28/78 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Football vs USC 11/4/78 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Football vsArizona State 11/11/78 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Football vs California 11/18/78 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Football Bluebonnet Bowl, Dec. 31, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Track Programs & Summaries - 1980 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Track Programs & Summaries - 1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Women's Track Programs & Summaries - 1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Track Programs & Summaries - 1978 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Japanese Volleyball Match, Feb. 24, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Men's basketball Non-League Game Statistics, Play by play, 1977-78 season (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Men's basketball vs California, Jan. 28 and Mar. 4, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Men's basketball vs Oregon State Jan. 6 and Feb. 18, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Men's basketball vs Oregon, Jan. 7 and Feb. 17, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Men's basketball vs Washington Jan. 14 and Feb. 23, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Men's basketball vs Washington State Jan. 13 and Feb. 25, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Men's basketball vs UCLA Feb. 3 and Feb. 11, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Men's basketball vs USC Feb. 4 and Feb. 10, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Football vs California 11/19/1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Football vs San Jose State 11/12/1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Football vs Tulane 9/17/1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Football vs Colorado 9/10/1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Football vs Illinois 9/24/1977 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Football vs Oregon 10/1/1977 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Football vs UCLA 10/8/1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Football vs Washington 10/15/1977 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Football vs Washington State 10/22/1977 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Football vs Oregon State 10/29/1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Football vs USC 11/5/1977 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Football vs Penn State 9/11/1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Football vs Michigan 9/18/1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Football vs San Jose 9/28/1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Football vs San Jose 9/28/1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Football vs Army 10/2/1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Football vs UCLA 10/9/1976 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Football vs Washington 10/16/1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Football vs Washington State 10/23/1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Football vs Oregon State 10/30/1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Football vs USC 11/6/1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Football vs Oregon 11/13/1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Football vs Oregon 11/16/1976 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Football vs Univ. of California 11/20/1976 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Football vs Penn State 9/13/1975 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Football vs Michigan 9/20/1975 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Football vs San Jose State 9/27/1975 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Football vs Army 10/4/1975 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Football vs UCLA 10/11/1975 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Football vs Washington 10/18/1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Football vs Washington State 10/25/1975 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Football vs Oregon State 11/1/1975 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Football vs USC 11/8/1975 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Football vs Oregon 11/15/1975 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Football vs California 11/22/1975 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Football, JV (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Football Alumni 5/10/1975 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Football vs Penn State 9/14/1974 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Football vs Illinois 9/21/1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Football vs Michigan 10/5/1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Football vs UCLA 10/12/1974 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Football vs Washington 10/19/1974 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Football vs Washington State 10/26/1974 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Football vs Oregon State 11/2/1974 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Football vs USC 11/9/1974 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Football vs California 11/23/1974 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Men's basketball vs Washington State, Jan. 6 and Feb. 19, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Men's basketball vs Washington Jan. 8 and Feb. 18, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Men's basketball vs UCLA Jan. 15 and Feb. 24, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Men's basketball vs USC Jan. 13 and Feb. 26, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Men's basketball vs Oregon Feb. 4 and Feb. 12, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Men's basketball vs Oregon State, Feb. 5 and Feb. 11, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Men's basketball vs California, Mar. 3 and Mar. 5, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Men's basketball PAC-8 1975-76 Boxes, Play-by-Play Programs (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Men's basketball Non-conference basketball, 1975-76 Boxes, Play-by-Play Programs (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Men's basketball non-league game statistics, play-by-play, 1976-77 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Men's basketball PAC-8 Basketball 1974-75 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Women's basketball stats, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Men's basketball non-league basketball 1974-75 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Additional Records, 1916-1988; Accession ARCH-1989-268
  - Misc. Stanford athletic publications, mostly media guides and informational packets on football, 1966-1988 (Box 1)
  - Cavalcade: Forty Years of Stanford Football, May 16, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Misc. football game programs, 1960-1974 (Box 1)
  - Pac-8 Track and Field Championships, May 19-20, 1972: program (Box 1)
  - Track and Field Performances Through the Years, Vol. 1, 1929-1936 (Assoc. of Track and Field Statisticians, c. 1984) (Box 1)
  - Pacific Coast Conference Records Book, 1916-1951 (Box 1)
  - Pacific Coast Conference Records Book, 1916-1955 (Box 1)
  - Big Bowl Football Guide, compiled and edited by Anthony C. DiMarco, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Scrapbook of newsclippings on women's sports at Stanford, 1964-74 (Box 2)
  - Scrapbook of newsclippings on women's sports at Stanford, 1974-75 (Box 2)
- Photographs, Accession ARCH-1989-271
  - Athletic Events (banquets, meetings, etc.) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Baseball - Individuals (Identified: N-Z) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Baseball - Individuals (Identified: A-M) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Baseball - Individuals (Unidentified) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Baseball - Staff (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Baseball - Teams (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Basketball - Action (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Basketball - Individuals (G. Andrews, R. Baker) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Basketball - Individuals (Clemetson, Doug & Don) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Basketball - Individuals (Cordles, Gowdy, Hamm) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Basketball - Individuals (Harrison, Hassen, Mallek) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Basketball - Individuals (Moore, Nisbet) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Basketball - Individuals (Rose, Talboy, Van Galder) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Basketball - Individuals (Unidentified) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Basketball - Staff (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Basketball - Teams (1) (Box 1, Folder 16-17)
  - Basketball - Teams & Individuals (Contact Sheets), 1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Basketball - Players & Games (Contact Sheets), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Boxing (4 unidentified students) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1953 Athletes (includes Skip Crist, Jack Shepard, Bob Mathias, Fred George, Howard Hertz, Nason Fishback (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Football - Action, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 3-5)
  - Football - Coach Dan Stavely (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Football - Individuals (includes Dick Ragsdale, Stoecker getting medal, Robin Moore, Jim Coffis, and possibly some of the Wow Boys as alums), 1960 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Football - Individuals (Arch, Brandin, Butler) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Football - Individuals (Conrad, Cummings) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Football - Individuals (Frasier, Harris) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Football - Individuals (Lewis, Lodato) (Box 2, Folder 11)